(Howard:)What do we owe you?
(Leonard:)It came to $28.17.
(Leonard:)Let's say six bucks apiece.
(Howard:)Here you go.
(Leonard:)Thank you.
(Penny:)What?
(Leonard:)Never mind. I got it.
(Penny:)Oh, you wanted me to pay.
(Leonard:)It's no big deal.
No, no, no, no.
You're right.
We're not going out anymore;
I should pay for myself.
(Penny:)What?
He said, "If he had
woman parts,
(Howard:)he'd eat for free
the rest of his life".
(Penny:)Yeah, but you wouldn't be able
to talk to yourself.
(Penny:)I'm a little low on cash.
(Leonard:)How much you got?
Nothing.
(Leonard:)How can you walk
around with no money?
(Penny:)I'm cute. I get by.
(Leonard:)It's okay,
you can owe me.
(Leonard:)Thank you.
Sheldon, six bucks.
(Sheldon:)No, thank you.
I'm not eating pizza tonight.
(Penny:)But it's Thursday.
(Penny:)Thursday's pizza night.
(Sheldon:)Not for me.
(Sheldon:)Thursday is now Cruciferous
Vegetable Night.